Erwin Chargaff Papers 1929-1992 Mss.B.C37
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1992; 30 linear feet
  - Friedman, Jacob, 1955 (Box 24)
  - Friedman, Ronald, 1975-1978 (Box 24)
  - Friedman, Samuel, 1952-1965 (Box 24)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Frisell, Wilhelm R., 1981 (Box 24)
  - Frøholm, L.O., 1961 (Box 24)
  - Fromageot, Claude, 1949-1952, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Fromageot, Pierre, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Fruton, Joseph S., 1952-1982 (Box 24)
  - Fujita, Akiji, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Fullbright, J. William, 1970 (Box 24)
  - Fuller, Buckminster, 1981, 1983 (Box 24)
  - Gaade, W., 1957 (Box 24)
    See also Ser.I, Biochimica et Biophysica
  - Gabriel, Othmar R., [196-], 1980 (Box 24)
  - Gaebler, O.H., 1949 (Box 24)
  - Gaito, John, 1961, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Gall, Joseph G., 1972 (Box 24)
  - Galler, William, 1954 (Box 24)
  - Galton, Suzanne A., 1964 (Box 24)
  - Gambino-Giuffrida, Angela, 1974-1979 (Box 25)
    Some in Italian
    Hayn, Elsa
    See also Ser.I, Connors, Catherine
    See also Ser.I, Hayn, Elsa
  - Gamow, George, 1954-1955; 21.0 Item(s) (Box 25)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Cytogenetics; Human genetics; Lectures, public speaking; Molecular genetics; Publication; RNA tie club
  - Gamow, Rustem Igor, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Gandelman, Bertha, 1951-1953 (Box 25)
  - Gandhi, P., 1977 (Box 25)
  - Gane and Ingram, Inc., 1956 (Box 25)
  - Garb, Solomon, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
  - Garcia, Alfredo Mariano, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Gardell, Sven, 1952 (Box 25)
  - Gardner, W.U., 1949-1950 (Box 25)
  - Garrigan, Owen Walter, 1957-1965 (Box 25)
  - Garvey, W.D., 1971 (Box 25)
  - Garzanti Editore, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Gasic, Gabriel, 1949 (Box 25)
  - Gasser, Herbert E., 1943 (Box 25)
  - George W. Gates and Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 25)
  - Gelineo, Stefan, 1949 (Box 25)
  - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1952, 1962, 1964 (Box 25)
  - General Biochemicals, Inc., 1952 (Box 25)
  - General Electric Company, 1947 (Box 25)
  - General Foods Corporation, 1946 (Box 25)
  - General Mills, Inc., 1957 (Box 25)
  - Geo, 1981 (Box 25)
  - Georgescu-Roegen, Nicholas, 1973, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Georgetown University, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Georgi, Siegfried, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Gerard, Ralph W., 1971 (Box 25)
  - Gerheim, Earl B., 1947 (Box 25)
  - Gessler, Albert E., 1944 (Box 25)
  - Gest, Howard, 1976 (Box 25)
    See also Ser.I, Indiana University
  - Ghiretti, Francesco, 1969-1972 (Box 25)
    Schreil, Werner
  - Ghosh, Ajit Kumar, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Ghosh, Jagat Jiban, 1952, 1959-1960 (Box 25)
  - Ghosh, Sudhamoy, 1954 (Box 25)
  - Giacomoni, Paolo, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Gierer, A., 1961 (Box 25)
  - Gilbert, Helen, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Gilde, Hans-Georg, 1975, 1977 (Box 25)
    See also Ser.I, Marietta College
  - Gilde, Helen C., 1978 (Box 25)
  - Gillespie, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 25)
  - Gilley, Frank P., 1953 (Box 25)
  - Gilman, Henry, 1965 (Box 25)
  - Gilman, William, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Gilson Medical Electronics, Inc., 1955, 1973, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Ginger, Leonard G., 1947 (Box 25)
  - Ginsberg, Steven, [1976] (Box 25)
  - Ginsburg, David, 1955 (Box 25)
  - Ginsburg, Sara, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Glaser, Robert J., 1968 (Box 25)
  - Glavind, Johs, 1948 (Box 25)
  - Glendening, Mary Beth, 1947 (Box 25)
  - Glick, Dudley Peters, 1946 (Box 25)
  - Gligoric, Velibor, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Glock, Gertrude E., 1953 (Box 25)
  - Gloor, H., 1953-1954 (Box 25)
    Benitez, Helena H.
  - Gobat, Charles, 1964-1965 (Box 25)
    In French and German
  - Godlowski, Z.Z., 1962 (Box 25)
  - Godly, A., 1954 (Box 25)
  - Goertzel, Mildred G., 1980, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Goettsch, Marianne, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Goetze-Claren, Wolfgang, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Gofman, John W., 1948 (Box 25)
  - Gold, Allen M., 1958, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Gold, Edwin R., 1947, 1954-1972 (Box 25)
    Kabat, Elvin A.
  - Goldberg, Leslie S., 1957 (Box 25)
  - Goldberg, Richard Barry, 1966-1979 (Box 25)
    Molholt, Bruce
    See also Ser.I, Brunngraber, Elinor
  - Goldenberg, Marcel, 1949 (Box 25)
  - Goldforb, A.J., 1948 (Box 25)
    See also Ser.I, Society for Experimental
  - Goldfrank, Helen Kay, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Goldin, Herzl, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Goldman, Dexter S., 1976 (Box 25)
  - Goldwater, William H., 1949 (Box 25)
  - Gollan, Frank, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Gollub, Seymour, 1949, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Gonçalves da Costa Lima, Joao Alfredo, 1959 (Box 25)
  - González, Manuel, 1955 (Box 25)
  - Goodenough, Ursula W., 1973, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Goodfield, June, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
  - Goodman, Fred, 1963, 1969 (Box 26)
    See also Ser.I, Saukkonen, Jussi J.
  - Goodman, Gabriel C., 1964 (Box 26)
  - Goodman, Irving, 1960, 1965-1968 (Box 26)
  - Goodwin, T.W., 1960-1961 (Box 26)
  - Gopalakrishna, Y., 1978 (Box 26)
  - Gordan, Charles Nathan, 1957-1958 (Box 26)
  - Gordan, Edward E., 1964 (Box 26)
  - Gordan, M., 1971-1972 (Box 26)
  - Gordan, Phillip N., 1980 (Box 26)
  - Gosálvez Y Galálvez, Mário, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Gottschalk, A., 1956, 1958 (Box 26)
  - Gourary, Paul, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Grabar, Pierre, 1965 (Box 26)
  - Graff, Samuel, 1955, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Graham, Loren, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  - Grandy, Lillian E., 1985 (Box 26)
  - Granick, Sam, 1959, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Grassé, Pierre P., 1973 (Box 26)
  - Gratzer, Walter B., 1968 (Box 26)
  - Gray, Ernest David, 1959-1963, 1968 (Box 26)
  - Gray, George W., 1951 (Box 26)
  - Green, Charlotte, 1948-1949, 1972-1979 (Box 26)
    Doniger, Ruth
    Foster, G.L.
    Magasanik, Boris
    Marshak, Celia Levine
    Rothe, Adelaide
    Zamenhof, Stephen
    See also Ser.I, Rothe, Adelaide
  - Green, David E., 1950-1955, 1962 (Box 26)
  - Green, G.H., 1977 (Box 26)
  - Green, Maurice, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Greenberg, David M., 1947, 1955, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Greenberg, Jerrold, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Greenstein, Jesse P., 1954 (Box 26)
  - Grégoire, Fleurette, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Gregor, Harry P., 1976 (Box 26)
  - Emil Greiner and Company, 1949, 1955 (Box 26)
  - Griffin and Tatlock Ltd., 1953-1954 (Box 26)
  - Gristede, Charlotte, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Groer, Francis, 1947 (Box 26)
  - Grokoest, Albert W., 1979, 1980, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Gros, François, 1954 (Box 26)
  - Gross, Ralph H., 1979 (Box 26)
  - Grossman, Albert, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Grossman, Lawrence, 1965-1966, 1972 (Box 26)
    Moldave, Kivie
  - Grundfest, Harry, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Gudernatsch, Friedrich, 1942-1958, 1962 (Box 26)
  - Guggenheim, M., 1946-1947 (Box 26)
  - Guha, Arabinda, 1968-1969 (Box 26)
  - Guha, B.C., 1958 (Box 26)
  - Günther, G., 1972 (Box 26)
  - Guranowski, Andrzej, 1978 (Box 26)
  - Gurin, Samuel, 1958 (Box 26)
  - Gurpide, Erlio, 1963 (Box 26)
  - Gurwitsch, A.A., 1958-1959 (Box 26)
  - Guschlbauer, Wilhelm, 1958-1959 (Box 26)
  - Gustafson, G., 1952 (Box 26)
  - Gustafson, Tryggve, 1949-1954 (Box 26)
  - Gustavson, K.H., 1962-1963, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Gutman, Alexander, B., 1953, 1968 (Box 26)
    See also Ser.I, Weissmann, Bernard
  - Haag, John, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Haberman, Vlastimil, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
  - Habif, David, 1948 (Box 26)
  - Hack, Marvin Howard, 1944-1952, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Hadd, John R., 1980 (Box 26)
  - Hadjiolov, A.A., 1979-1980 (Box 26)
  - Haffkine Institute, 1952 (Box 26)
  - Hafner, Fred H., 1954 (Box 26)
  - Haggis, G.H., 1973 (Box 26)
  - Hahn, Ralf, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Hais, I.M., 1951 (Box 26)
  - Hakala, Rino W., 1952 (Box 27)
  - Hakim, Anwar A., 1957 (Box 27)
  - Hakim, M.A., 1960 (Box 27)
  - Halbert, Seymour P., 1961 (Box 27)
  - Halpern, Bernard, 1967 (Box 27)
  - Hamburger, Viktor, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Hamel, Ernest, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Hamer, Douglas, 1955 (Box 27)
  - Hammarsten, Einar, 1953 (Box 27)
    See also Ser.I, Nobel Foundation
  - Hammer, Miriam, 1943 (Box 27)
  - Hanahan, Donald J., 1961 (Box 27)
  - Handler, Philip, 1965 (Box 27)
  - Hanes, C.S., 1949 (Box 27)
  - Hanes, Charles S., 1953-1954 (Box 27)
  - Hanger, F.M., 1943 (Box 27)
  - Hanovia Chemical and Manufacturing Company, 1946 (Box 27)
  - Happold, Frank C., 1956 (Box 27)
  - Hardin, Garrett, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Harding, Clifford V., 1961 (Box 27)
  - Harfmann, Fritz, 1952-1953 (Box 27)
  - Harington, Charles, 1952 (Box 27)
  - Edward S. Harkness Eye Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Harner, Pearl, 1970 (Box 27)
  - Harper, Edwin T., 1975 (Box 27)
  - Harper's, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Harrington, Robert K., 1975 (Box 27)
  - Harris, Marvin, 1975 (Box 27)
  - Harris, Robert S., 1948-1953, 1963 (Box 27)
  - Harris, T.N., 1947 (Box 27)
  - Harrison, Stephen, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Harrow, Benjamin, 1956, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Harshaw Chemical Company, 1953 (Box 27)
  - Hart, Roger G., 1973 (Box 27)
  - Harte, Robert A., 1965 (Box 27)
  - Hartman, Karl A., 1971 (Box 27)
  - Hartman, Philip E., 1977 (Box 27)
    Sinsheimer, Robert L.
  - Hartwick College, 1971-1973 (Box 27)
  - Harvard Medical School, 1983-1984 (Box 27)
  - Harvey, Brian, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Harvey Society, 1947-1984 (Box 27)
    Dubos, René
    Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
  - Hasegawa, Takezi, 1963 (Box 27)
  - Hashimoto, Tamotsu, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Hashimoto, Yohei, 1955 (Box 27)
  - Hassel, O., 1953 (Box 27)
  - Hastings Center, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Hauptman, Herbert A., 1978 (Box 27)
  - Hauptmann, Henrique, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Haurowitz, Felix, 1950-1960 (Box 27)
    See also Ser.I, New York Academy of Sciences
  - Hauschka, Theodore S., 1945 (Box 27)
    See also Ser.I, Toennies, Gerrit
  - Hausman, David Louis, 1965-1967 (Box 27)
  - Hawthorne, John Nigel (Box 27)
    - Folder #1, 1951-1967 (Box 27)
    - Folder #2, 1968-1984 (Box 27)
  - Hayashi, Akira, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. (Box 27)
    See Ser.I, Stourzh, Gerald
  - Hayes, Robert, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Hayn, Elsa (Box 28)
    Gambino-Giuffrida, Angela, 1978
    Karkas, John D., 1969, 1975
    Lin, Hsiang Ju, 1973
    Martucci, Charles M., 1971
    Wu, Anna Fang, 1971
    See also Ser.I, Gambino-Giuffrida, Angela
    - Folder #1, 1969-1975 (Box 28)
    - Folder #2, 1976-1984 (Box 28)
  - Haywood, Anne Mowbray, 1961-1973 (Box 28)
    See also Ser.IIa, American Cancer Society,
  - Head, J.F., 1948 (Box 28)
  - Hebrew University, 1949-1950 (Box 28)
  - Hecht, E., 1946, 1948, 1963 (Box 28)
  - Hechter, Oscar, 1963-1964 (Box 28)
  - Hechtman, Peter, 1963 (Box 28)
  - Heidelberger, Charles, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1942-1957, 1983 (Box 28)
    Industrial and Engineering News
  - Heifetz, Harold, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Heilbrunn, L.V., 1948, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Heineken, H.P., 1964 (Box 28)
  - H.P. Heineken Prize, 1964-1985 (Box 28)
    Feith, P.R.
    See also Ser.IIb, III, VI, same title
  - Heinz, Jenny, 1962 (Box 28)
  - Hellemans, Alexander, 1978, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Heller, Erich, 1980, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Heller, F. Thomas, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Hellerman, Leslie, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Helpern, 1948 (Box 28)
  - Henderson, Anne, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Hendricks, S.B., 1954 (Box 28)
  - Hendry, Lawrence B., 1984 (Box 28)
    Bransome, Edwin D., Jr.
  - Hennessey, Gilbert, 1981 (Box 28)
  - Heplar, Joseph Q., 1964 (Box 28)
  - Heppel, Leon A., 1951-1960, 1964 (Box 28)
  - Herbert, Victor, 1972 (Box 28)
  - Herbst, Robert M., 1953 (Box 28)
  - Herder and Herder, 1969-1973 (Box 28)
    See also Ser.I, Seabury Press
  - Herman, Norman Laurence, 1967 (Box 28)
  - Herman, William S., 1968 (Box 28)
  - Hermann, 1972 (Box 28)
  - Herr, Earl B., Jr., 1960 (Box 28)
  - Herriott, Roger M., 1948 (Box 28)
  - Herrmann, Heinz, 1954, 1961 (Box 28)
  - Herrmann, Klaus, 1978 (Box 28)
  - Herrmann, R., 1952 (Box 28)
  - Hershey, A.D., 1958 (Box 28)
  - Herzberg, Robert M., 1959 (Box 28)
  - Hess, Eugene L., 1948, 1970 (Box 28)
  - Hess, Ninon, 1954 (Box 28)
  - Heumann, Karl F., 1978 (Box 28)
  - Hevesy, G., 1950-1966 (Box 28)
  - Heyrovsky, Antonin, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Hickrill Chemical Research Foundation, Inc., 1951-1955 (Box 28)
  - Hiebert, Erwin N., 1979 (Box 28)
  - Hildebrandt, Sue A., 1971 (Box 28)
  - Hildinger, Manfred K., 1958 (Box 28)
  - Hill, Arthur J., 1943 (Box 28)
  - Hill, D.D., 1962 (Box 28)
  - Hillaby, John D., 1956 (Box 28)
  - Himes, Hillard W., 1951 (Box 29)
  - Himwich, Harold E., 1967 (Box 29)
  - Himwich, Williamina A., 1964 (Box 29)
  - Hirsch, James G., 1973 (Box 29)
  - Hirsch, Jerry, 1975-1982 (Box 29)
  - Hirsch, Julius, 1950-1951, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Hirschberg, Erich, 1965, 1968 (Box 29)
  - Hirt, Bernhard, 1968 (Box 29)
  - Histochemical Society, 1949-1954 (Box 29)
    Lillie, R.D.
  - Hitchings, George H., 1952 (Box 29)
    See also Ser.I, Wellcome Research
  - Hjort, Peter, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Hoagland, Mahlon B., 1977-1982 (Box 29)
  - Hoberman, Henry D., 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Hoch, Hans, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Hochberg, Eric, 1969 (Box 29)
  - Hochstein, Paul E., [196-] (Box 29)
  - Hodes, Marion Edward, 1949-1976 (Box 29)
  - Hodgkin, Dorothy Crowfoot, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Hoff, Herma C., 1961 (Box 29)
  - Hoffman, Philip, [196-] (Box 29)
  - Hoffman, Robert, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Hoffmann, Silke E.M., 1965-1968 (Box 29)
  - Hoffmann-LaRoche, Inc., 1942-1971 (Box 29)
    Aeschlimann, J.A.
  - Hoffmann-Ostenhof, O., 1958, 1967 (Box 29)
  - Hofmann, Klaus, 1963, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Hofschneider, P.H., 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Hogeboom, George H., 1952-1955 (Box 29)
  - Hogenkamp, H.P.C., 1972 (Box 29)
  - Hokin, Lowell E., 1951, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Holder, Ian A., 1960 (Box 29)
  - Holiday, Ensor R., 1951-1954 (Box 29)
  - Hollaender, Alexander, 1964 (Box 29)
    See also Ser.I, International Symposium on Nuclear Physiology and Differentiation
  - Hollander, Franklin, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Holman, Ralph T., 1953 (Box 29)
  - Holmes, Barbara E., 1948 (Box 29)
  - Holmgren, Nils, 1950 (Box 29)
  - Holter, Heinz, 1949-1952, 1960 (Box 29)
  - Holtfreter, Johannes, 1946-1947 (Box 29)
  - Holy, A., 1970 (Box 29)
  - Horder, T.J., 1980 (Box 29)
  - Horecker, B.L., 1962 (Box 29)
  - Horiuchi, Tadao, 1959, 1962 (Box 29)
  - Hornig, Donald F., 1965 (Box 29)
  - Horowitz, Jack, 1955-1966, 1971 (Box 29)
    Bloch, Emmy, 1958
    Shemin, David
    See also Ser.I, Mackenzie, Jean
  - Horowitz, Martin I., 1963 (Box 29)
  - Horrobin, David F., 1976 (Box 29)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr., 1961, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Hörstadius, Sven, 1949-1954 (Box 29)
  - Louisa Gross Horwitz Prize Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 29)
    McGill, William J.
  - Hoshishima, Keiichiro, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Hoskin, Francis C.G., 1964 (Box 29)
  - Hotchkiss, R.D., 1954 (Box 29)
    See Ser.I, Lipshitz, Rakoma
  - Hotchkiss, Rollin D., 1949-1955, 1971, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Hougen, Frithjof W., 1957 (Box 29)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Huang, Henry H., 1972 (Box 30)
  - Hubbard, Ruth, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Huber, Wolfgang, 1951 (Box 30)
  - Huberman, Barbara, 1954 (Box 30)
  - Hudson, Howard M., 1950 (Box 30)
  - Huennekens, Frank M., 1964, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Hufnagel, Dorothy Anne, 1961, 1963 (Box 30)
  - Human Nature, 1978-1979 (Box 30)
  - Humana Press, Inc., 1977 (Box 30)
  - L'Humanité, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1965 (Box 30)
  - Hurlbert, Robert B., 1967 (Box 30)
  - Hurlbert, Ronald E., 1959 (Box 30)
  - Hurvich, Leo M., 1968 (Box 30)
  - Huskins, C. Leonard, 1950 (Box 30)
  - Hutchinson, William C., 1958 (Box 30)
  - Hutner, S.H., 1962 (Box 30)
    Pogo, Angel Oscar
  - Hydén, Holger, 1953, 1962 (Box 30)
  - Hygrade Food Products Corporation, 1947 (Box 30)
  - Ikeda, Yonosuke, 1960 (Box 30)
  - Imperial Chemical Industries Limited, 1947 (Box 30)
  - India. American Consulate in Bombay, 1952 (Box 30)
  - India. Embassy, 1959 (Box 30)
    See also Ser.IIb, India. All India Institute
  - Indian Institute of Science, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Indiana University, 1970 (Box 30)
    Gest, Howard
  - Indovina, Ignazio, 1951 (Box 30)
  - Ingram, Charlotte Ann, 1963 (Box 30)
  - Institut Culturel Franco-Allemand, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Institut de Biologie Physico-Chimique, 1961-1962 (Box 30)
  - Institut Für Mikrobiologie und Experimentelle Therapie, 1950, 1960-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institute for Cancer Research, 1972, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Institute for Cultural Progress, 1981, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Institute for Medical Research, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Institute for Muscle Research, 1949-1950 (Box 30)
  - Institute of International Education, 1946-1953, 1976-1977 (Box 30)
  - Integral, 1980 (Box 30)
  - International Association of Microbiologists, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - International Biographical Archives and Dictionary of Central European Emigrés, 1933-1945, 1978 (Box 30)
  - International Botanical Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 30)
    See also Ser.IIb, International Botanical
  - International Cancer Congress, 1957-1958 (Box 30)
    Work, T.S.
  - International Chemical and Nuclear Corporation, 1970 (Box 30)
  - International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences, 1976-1982 (Box 30)
  - International Conference on Thrombosis and Embolism, 1953-1955 (Box 30)
  - International Congress for Experimental Cytology, 1946-1948 (Box 30)
  - International Congress for Microbiology, 1953 (Box 30)
  - International Congress of Biochemistry, 1949, 1957-1970 (Box 30)
    Handler, Philip
    Hoffmann-Ostenhof, O.
    Kratky, O.
    Moore, Stanford
    Ochoa, Severo, 1960
    Weissmann, Charles
    See also Ser.IIb, International Congress of Biochemistry
  - International Equipment Company, 1942-1952 (Box 30)
  - International Laboratory of Genetics and Biophysics, 1966 (Box 30)
    Buzzati-Traverso, A.A.
    Scarano, Eduardo
  - International Milling Company, 1957 (Box 30)
  - International Science Foundation, 1970 (Box 30)
  - International Society for Research in Frontiers of Medicine, 1976-1977 (Box 30)
  - International Society of Hematology, 1957-1959 (Box 30)
    Polli, Elio E.
  - International Symposium on Nuclear Physiology and Differentiation, 1967-1968 (Box 31)
    Hollaender, Alexander
  - International Symposium on the Chemistry of Natural Products, 1962 (Box 31)
  - International Symposium on the Origin of Life, 1956-1957 (Box 31)
    Oparin, A.I.
  - International Union of Biochemistry, 1956-1960 (Box 31)
    Thompson, R.H.S.
  - International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 1958-1959 (Box 31)
  - International Who's Who, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Interscience Publishers, Inc., 1944-1954 (Box 31)
  - Ip, Peter M.K., 1967 (Box 31)
  - Iragorri, Edgar, 1953 (Box 31)
  - Ireland, Treadwell L., 1978 (Box 31)
  - Irsigler, F.J., 1975 (Box 31)
  - Isaacs, Hart, Jr., 1958 (Box 31)
  - Ishida, Masahiro Rue, 1960-1961 (Box 31)
  - Istituto Della Enciclopedia Italiana, 1970-1977 (Box 31)
  - Istituto Lombardo di Scienze e Lettere, 1954-1955, 1961 (Box 31)
  - Istituto Sieroterapico Milanese, 1959 (Box 31)
    De Barbieri, A.
  - Ivánovics, György, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Ivantzov, Dimitri N., 1963 (Box 31)
  - Jackson, Wes, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Jacob, François, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Jacob, Miriam I., 1953 (Box 31)
  - Jacobson, M.M., 1957 (Box 31)
  - Jacoby, Kurt, 1958, 1963-1964 (Box 31)
  - Jacoli, Giulio G., 1960 (Box 31)
  - Jacot, Claude, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Jaenicke, Rainer, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Jagger, John, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Jahn-Osersky, M., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Jahnig, Erna, 1959-1960 (Box 31)
  - Jakobson, Roman, 1976-1977 (Box 31)
  - James, D. Geraint, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Janes, Donald W., 1962 (Box 31)
  - Jánszky, B., 1950 (Box 31)
  - Jaques, L.B., 1945 (Box 31)
  - Jardetzky, Christine D., 1973 (Box 31)
  - Jarosch, Robert, 1966, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1965, 1975 (Box 31)
  - Jayaraman, R., 1961 (Box 31)
  - Jeanloz, Roger William, 1947, 1960-1961 (Box 31)
  - Jeener, R., 1955 (Box 31)
  - Jehle, Herbert, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Jeljaszewicz, Janusz, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Jenkins, John B., 1977 (Box 31)
  - Jensen, Elwood V., 1976 (Box 31)
  - Jervis, George A., 1958 (Box 31)
  - Jirgensons, Bruno, 1958-1974 (Box 31)
  - John, K.V., 1971 (Box 31)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1951-1956, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Johnson, Edward A., 1951-1954 (Box 31)
  - Johnson, T.B., 1947 (Box 31)
  - Johnston, William M., 1977 (Box 31)
  - Jonas, F., 1943 (Box 31)
  - Jones, Evan E., 1975-1976 (Box 31)
  - Jones, Hardin B., 1955 (Box 31)
    See also Ser.I, White House Conference on
  - Jonnard, Raymond, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Jordan, D.O., 1948-1960 (Box 31)
  - Jordan, Helene J., 1983 (Box 31)
  - Jorpes, J. Erik, 1947, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Joshi, Krishna C., 1957 (Box 32)
  - Joshi, Sudha, 1956 (Box 32)
  - Josse, John W., 1960 (Box 32)
  - Jossey-Bass, Allen, 1980 (Box 32)
  - The Journal of Biological Chemistry (Box 32)
    Brawerman, George, 1954
    Green, David E.
    Heppel, Leon A.
    Horowitz, Jack, 1960
    Lipshitz, Rakoma, 1954
    Meister, Alton, 1960
    See also Ser.I, Brawerman, George
    - Folder #1, 1942-1950 (Box 32)
    - Folder #2, 1951-1956 (Box 32)
    - Folder #3, 1957-1978 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Biophysical and Biochemical Cytology, 1957, 1959 (Box 32)
  - The Journal of Cell Biology, 1964 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Cellular Physiology, 1970 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Clinical Investigation, 1948-1962 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Colloid Science, 1956 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Histochemistry and Cytochemistry, 1954 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Neurochemistry, 1957, 1960 (Box 32)
    Sperry, Warren M.
  - Journal of Nutrition, 1961 (Box 32)
  - Journal of Polymer Science, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Journal of the American Chemical Society, 1943-1960 (Box 32)
    See also Ser.I, Brown, George B.
  - Journal of the National Cancer Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 32)
  - Judson, Horace, 1976-1981; 10.0 Item(s) (Box 32)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Chargaff, Erwin; Crick, Francis H. C.; History of biology, especially genetics; Molecular genetics; Pauling, Linus; Publication -- The Eighth Day of Creation; Requests for reprints; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Watson, James D.
  - Jukes, Thomas H., 1963, 1968 (Box 32)
  - Jung, Jia Ying, 1961 (Box 32)
  - Kabat, Elvin A., 1958-1980 (Box 32)
    See also Ser.I, Gold, Edwin R.
  - Kabeya-N'Galula, Babo, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Kacser, Henrik, 1956 (Box 32)
  - Kaesberg, Paul, 1961 (Box 32)
    Stacey, K.A.
    See also Ser.I, Stacey, K.A.
  - Kagan, Fred, 1964 (Box 32)
  - Kagan, Jerome, 1971 (Box 32)
  - Kahane, Ernest, 1967-1971 (Box 32)
  - Kahn, Jennifer Bronwen, 1967-1970 (Box 32)
    See Ser.I, Nielsen, Jennifer Bronwen
  - Kahn, Kenneth, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Kahng, H., 1963 (Box 32)
    See also Ser.I, Shemin, David
  - Kalckar, Herman M., 1945, 1955-1959 (Box 32)
  - Kamen, Martin (Box 33)
    See Ser.I, Cori, Carl F.
  - Kamiya, 1963 (Box 33)
  - Kamm, O., 1943 (Box 33)
  - Kanabrocki, Eugene, 1948 (Box 33)
  - Kanazir, Dusan, 1952-1953, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
  - Kaplan, Frank E., 1946 (Box 33)
  - Kaplan, Henry, 1954 (Box 33)
  - Kaplan, Nathan O., 1953 (Box 33)
    See also Ser.I, Brandeis University
  - Kapoor, N.K., 1964 (Box 33)
  - Kapoor, Pushkar Raj, 1974 (Box 33)
  - Kapuler, Alan M., [1971] (Box 33)
  - Karkas, Carmen, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Karkas, John D., 1957-1980 (Box 33)
    Brunngraber, Elinor
    See also Ser.I, Rudner, Rivka
  - Karlin, Arthur, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Karp, Adele, 1943 (Box 33)
  - Karshan, Maxwell, 1959 (Box 33)
  - Kasten, Frederic, H., 1983 (Box 33)
  - Kastenbaum, Marvin A., 1971 (Box 33)
  - Katchalski, Aaron, 1952-1961 (Box 33)
  - Katchalski, Ephraim, 1951-1956, 1965 (Box 33)
    See also Ser.I, Weizmann Institute
    of
  - Kathawala, F.G., 1967 (Box 33)
  - Kato, Katsuji, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Katz, Sidney, 1962 (Box 33)
  - Kauffman, George B., 1976 (Box 33)
  - Kauffman, F., 1946-1947 (Box 33)
  - Kavanau, J.L., 1954 (Box 33)
  - Kawada, Minoru, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Kawade, Y., 1959 (Box 33)
  - Kay, Ernest R.M., 1985 (Box 33)
  - Kaye, Gordan I., 1968, 1975 (Box 33)
  - Kazal, Louis A., 1948 (Box 33)
  - Kehlmann, Lilly, 1954 (Box 33)
  - Keiles, Elsa O., 1954 (Box 33)
  - Keilin, D., 1952 (Box 33)
  - Kellenberger, E., 1963 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg Company, 1957 (Box 33)
  - Kemo, Carolyn E., 1978 (Box 33)
  - Kendall, Forrest E., 1940 (Box 33)
  - Kendrew, John C., 1951-1974 (Box 33)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1965 (Box 33)
  - Kennedy, Poindexter J., 1980 (Box 33)
  - Kennedy, William H., 1958 (Box 33)